cdac.in 2009-04-19

# C-DAC: Privacy Policy

This legal notice pertains to C-DAC Web site " www.cdac.in" here after referred to as "this Web site".

**Welcome**

This site is owned by Centre for Development of Advanced Computing ("C-DAC"). C-DAC would like to safeguard the information you provide to us about yourself. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using, or submitting information, to this site. **Use of this site constitutes your consent to our Privacy Policy**. Topics included in this policy are:

  * Your Consent
  * Active Information Collection
  * Passive Information Collection
  * Use and Disclosure of Information
  * Links from Other Web Sites
  * Access and Correction
  * Security
  * Other Terms
  * How to Contact Us
  * Change to This Privacy Policy

Your Consent

By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Active Information Collection

Like many Web sites, this site actively collects information from its visitors by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail and feedback forms. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and so on).

Some areas of this site may require you to submit information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions, order processing, submitting a resume). You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional.

Passive Information Collection

As you navigate through a Web site, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as navigational data collection.

This site may use **Internet Protocol (IP) addresses**. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet and is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases an IP address is dynamic (changing each time you connect to the Internet), rather than static (unique to a particular user's computer). We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our site, and administer and improve the site.

Use and Disclosure of Information

Except as otherwise stated, we may use your information to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes (could be on users demographics, interests and behaviour), and for providing you with the latest information for direct marketing purposes where we think you may be interested in the products and services of some of our affiliates or third parties. Your right to choose is important to us though, so, if you do not wish to receive information about other products & services from C-DAC or other parties, you can always contact our Privacy Compliance Manager (Click here to send an eMail).

If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We will take reasonable measures to prevent personally identifiable information from being combined with passively collected information, unless you consent otherwise.

C-DAC may disclose your personally identifiable information to other C-DAC affiliates worldwide that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties, located in India and/or any other country, but only

> (i) to contractors we use to support our business (e.g., fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy;
> 
> (ii) in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; or
> 
> (iii) where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations. In addition, we will make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not in personally identifiable form.

Links from Other Web Sites

Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The data protection practices of those Web sites linked to C-DAC are not covered by this policy statement. You are advised to check the data protection policies of these third party Web sites yourself before using those sites.

Access and Correction

To keep your personally identifiable information accurate, current, and complete, please contact our Privacy Compliance Manager. A reasonable administration fee may be charged for providing you with access to the personal data in order for us to process such correction request.

Security

We take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no data transmissions over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, C-DAC cannot ensure or warranty the security of any information you transmit to us via the internet, and you do so at your own risk. Once we have received your transmission, we will use our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

Other Terms

Your use of this site is subject to our Legal Notice.

How to Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, please use "contact us" link on this Web site or contact us at :

**Centre for Development of Advanced Computing (C-DAC)** ,  
(A Scientific Society of Department of Information Technology, Government of India)  
Pune University Campus,  
Ganesh Khind,  
Pune 411 007.  
Telephone: +91-20-2569 4000 / 2569 4001 2569 4002 / 2569 4003 2569 4005 / 2569 4006  
Fax: +91-20-2569 4059

Changes to This Privacy Policy

If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information.

Last updated :Wednesday, January 23, 2008
